接线员，你能帮我接佛罗里达州伊斯拉莫拉达的快递局吗?
Operator, haven't you been able to get me the express office at Islamorada, Florida yet?
是的，我知道从伦敦打电话到美国需要时间。
Yes, I know it takes time to call from London to the States.
但请快点。这非常重要!
But please hurry. It's terribly important!
接电话。
Answer that phone.
快去开门!
Answer the bell!
接电话!
Answer the phone!
你想让我先回答哪一个?两个都是。
Which do you want me to answer first? Both of 'em.
都是，都是!
Both of 'em. Both of 'em!
请稍等。谢谢你！
Hold the line, please. Thank you.
我想握住你的手。是的,女士。
I'd like to have my grip, please. Yes, ma'am.
让我看看。他们是乘最后一班火车来的。
Let me see that. Well, they came in on the last train.
我们还没有把卡车上的东西卸下来。出去把那位女士抓住。
We haven't unloaded the truck yet. Go out and get the lady's grip.
快点。
Hurry up.
-不好意思…-打扰一下。
- Excuse me... - Excuse me, please.
女士，这是你的包。
Lady, here's your bag.
你想干什么，毁了这位女士的行李吗?
What are you trying to do, ruin the lady's baggage?
它在哪里?这一个。
Where is it? This one.
给您，夫人。我很抱歉。谢谢你！
There you are, Madam. I'm sorry. Thank you.
来吧，把这些都清理干净。来吧，把它弄清楚。
Now come on, clean this all up. Come on, straighten it out.
威尔伯，亲爱的，你没事吧?
Wilbur, darling, are you all right?
桑德拉，我伤了我可怜的小脑袋。
Sandra, I hurt my poor little head.
你的头吗?
Your head?
哦,不。
Oh, no.
疼吗?嗯。
Does this hurt? Uh-uh.
Does that hurt? Uh-uh.
谢天谢地。
Thank heaven.
如果你有什么三长两短，最亲爱的，我永远也不会原谅自己。
If anything happened to you, dearest, I'd never forgive myself.
那个吻让一切都好起来了。
That kiss made everything all better.
你很担心我，对吧?
You worry about me an awful lot, don't you?
你对我来说很重要。
You mean an awful lot to me.
告诉我更多。
Tell me more.
我会的。今晚的晚餐。
I will. At dinner tonight.
好的。
Okay.
来吧，从那里起来，去工作!
Come on, get up out of there and go to work!
也就是说，如果你的头脑不太困扰你的话。
That is, if your head doesn't bother you too much.
他的头没事。是吗?你的头还好吗?
His head is all right. It is, eh? But is your head all right?
当然可以。坦白地说，我不明白。
Certainly. Frankly, I don't get it.
坦白地说，你永远不会知道。
And frankly, you never will.
我不能理解那个女人。
I can't understand that dame.
在这里的所有男人中，那道上等菜偏偏挑出了像你这样的人。
Of all the guys around here, that classy dish has to pick out a guy like you.
这有什么不对吗?改天去照照镜子吧。
What's wrong with that? Go look at yourself in the mirror sometime.
我为什么要伤害自己的感情?
Why should I hurt my own feelings?
去接电话。去吧，我来拿。
Go answer the phone. Go ahead, I'll pick these up.
行李的房间。
Baggage room.
伦敦吗?打电话吗?
London? Calling here?
这不是收钱的，对吧?
This ain't collect, is it?
哦，好吧。让他接电话。
Oh, all right. Put him on.
喂?你有两个寄给麦克道格恐怖屋的箱子吗?
Hello? Do you have two crates addressed to the McDougal House of Horrors?
支票上的数字是多少?没关系。
What's the number on the checks? Never mind that.
今晚，这里将是满月。我没有多少时间。
Tonight, the moon will be full here. I haven't much time.
现在，仔细听。我天亮就飞出去。
Now, listen closely. I'm flying out of here at dawn.
在我到达之前，无论如何你都不能把那些箱子送出去。
Under no circumstances are you to deliver those crates until I arrive.
明白吗?下……
Understand? Under...
麦克道格尔先生，你能不能别漱口了?
Mr. McDougal, will you stop gargling your throat?
嘿，你得让你的狗离电话远点。
Hey, you'll have to get your dog away from the phone.
你说的话我一个字都听不见。
I can't hear a word you're sayin'.
你大老远从伦敦给我打电话，就为了让你的狗跟我说话，真是太蠢了。
You're awful silly to call me all the way from London, just to have your dog talk to me.
这是很棒的对话。那家伙像狼一样咆哮。
That's great conversation. The guy growls like a wolf.
有些人胆子真大!
The nerve of some people!
有什么事吗，小子?我赶时间。
Well, what can I do for you, bub? I'm in a hurry.
我这里有两个箱子，寄给我的恐怖之屋，我要马上送货。我叫麦克道格尔。
I have two crates here addressed to my House of Horrors, and I want immediate delivery. My name's McDougal.
麦克道戈尔?但是，我刚刚在伦敦和你通过电话。
McDougal? But, I just talked to you on the telephone from London.
你怎么这么快就到了?他们用大炮射你吗?
How'd you get here so fast? They shoot you out of a cannon?
你疯了吗?我一直都在这里。
Are you crazy? I've been here all the time.
现在，把那些箱子给我拿来!
Now, get me those crates!
你在这里多久了?五分钟。
How long you been here? Five minutes.
你在抱怨什么?我在这里5年了，你没见过我像那样走来走去，大喊大叫……这是保险单，这是提单。
What are you beefing about? I've been here five years, you don't see me going around like that and yelling... There's the insurance slip and there's the bill of lading.
现在把那些箱子给我拿来!
Now get me those crates!
听着，你能不能别嚷嚷了?
Look, will you please stop yellin'?
到这里来。你知道，大声说话是不礼貌的。
Come here. You know, it's impolite to raise your voice.
哦,小鸡!
Oh, Chick!
你一开始为什么不给我这个?
Why didn't you give me these in the first place?
气……小妞，这个人想要这些箱子。
Chi... Chick, this man wants these crates.
嗯。投保2万美元。我们最好查一下。
Hmm. Insured for $20,000. We'd better look these up.
一定很有价值。我会说它们很有价值。
Must be valuable. I'll say they're valuable.
威尔伯?是的,桑德拉?
Wilbur? Yes, Sandra?
他很忙，很忙。拜托。
He's busy, he's busy. Please.
那个小家伙真是不可理喻。快点搬那些箱子!
That little fellow's impossible. Hurry up with those crates!
你知道我在里面装了什么吗，小姐?我一点也不知道。
Do you know what I've got in there, miss? Haven't the slightest idea.
只是恐怖屋有史以来最吸引人的地方，仅此而已。
Just the greatest attraction the House of Horrors ever had, that's all.
其中一具棺材里装着德古拉伯爵的遗体。
One of them's a coffin containing the remains of the original Count Dracula.
另一个是弗兰肯斯坦怪物的尸体。
And the other's the body of the Frankenstein Monster.
我猜这个组合足够吓到裤子了…我是说，毫不费力，不是吗?
Guess that combination's enough to scare the pants... I mean, shirt right off your back, ain't it?
我不容易被吓到。在钱的问题上，我也没有。
I don't scare easily. Neither do I, where money's concerned.
我买的很便宜。欧洲探员凭空挑了我的名字。
I got 'em dirt cheap. European agent picked my name right out of thin air.
很有趣。是的。
Very interesting. Yeah.
麦克道戈尔先生。
Mr. McDougal.
嘿，奇克，这有一个。
Hey, Chick, here's one.
亲爱的……是吗?
Darling... Yeah?
亲爱的，我得走了。出了点事。
Darling, I have to run along. Something's come up.
那意味着我们今晚的约会要取消了。
That means we'll have to break our date tonight.
不会是另一个男人吧?当然不是。
It ain't another man, is it? Of course not.
愚蠢的男孩。哦,是的。
Silly boy. Oh, yeah.
男孩，我漂浮在爱的云上。
Boy, I'm floatin' on a cloud of love.
听着，你这个小飞艇，如果你不帮我一把，我马上就把你的气放掉。
Listen, you little blimp, I'll let the air out of you in a minute, if you don't give me a hand.
你明白吗?谢谢你！
You understand that? Thank you.
天啊，这孩子迷路了。
Boy, is this kid lost.
到这里来。拿着绳子爬到箱子顶上，把它绑在上面的把手上。
Come here. Take that rope and get up on top that box, and tie it to that handle up there.
好的。什么都不重要了。
Okay. Nothing matters no more.
我太高兴了。去吧，上去!
I'm so happy. Go on, get up there!
给你。
Here it is.
现在别动。
Hold still now.
哦!
Oh!
小鸡!
Chick!
阻止他!他是想毁了我吗?
Stop him! Is he trying to ruin me?
保持冷静。你的保险。
Keep your shirt on. You're insured.
是的，如果那些展品被损坏了，我打算去收集。
Yes, and if those exhibits are damaged, I intend to collect.
好了，你来了。我把它包起来好吗?不，你这个白痴。
Well, there you are. Shall I wrap it up? No, you idiot.
你要把它们拿到我的恐怖之屋然后把它们卸下来。
You're gonna take those down to my House of Horrors and uncrate them.
因为如果你们这样处理行李的话，我会让那里的保险代理人在我收货之前检查一下。
Because if that's the way you handle baggage, I'm going to have the insurance agent there to inspect them before I accept delivery.
那你得付加班费因为我是工会成员。
Well, then it's gonna cost you overtime because I'm a union man.
我每天只工作16个小时。
And I work only 16 hours a day.
工会成员每天只工作8小时。
A union man only works eight hours a day.
我属于两个工会!
I belong to two unions!
-把这些拿到我家去!-好吧。
- Get those down to my place! -  All right.
嘿，威尔伯，这是钥匙。打开门。
Hey, Wilbur, here's a key. Open the door.
我不会喜欢这样的。来，帮我一把。
I'm not gonna like this. Come on, gimme a hand.
来吧，拿进去。
Come on, get it inside.
好吧，拉!你想让我做所有的工作吗?
Well, pull it! You want me to do all the work?
来吧，帮我一把，好吗?
Come on, help me with it, will ya?
哦……现在又怎么了?
Oh... What's the matter now?
有人在背后捅我一刀。哦,胡说!
Somebody's got a knife in my back. Oh, nonsense!
开关在哪里?这里。
Where's the switch? Here.
桑德拉现在应该看到你了。
Sandra should see you now.
转身。看看你在害怕什么。
Turn around. Look what you're afraid of.
转身!
Turn around!
来吧，站起来。这只是个假人。
Come on, get up on your feet. It's only a dummy.
假的。它很聪明，能吓到我。
Dummy nothin'. It was smart enough to scare me.
来吧，抓住盒子。去做吧。
Come on, get a hold of the box. Go ahead.
好了，来吧，转过来。
All right, come on, swing it around.
好吧，帮点忙吧!
Well, help a little bit!
哦,哦!
Oh, oh!
来吧，你这个胆小鬼。这些东西伤害不了你。
Come on, you fraidy-cat. These things can't harm ya.
它们是用蜡做的。
They're made out of wax.
你知道吗，人们给麦克道格尔现金，让他来这里吓一跳?
You know, people pay McDougal cash to come in here and get scared?
我在欺骗他。我在无缘无故地害怕。
I'm cheatin' him. I'm gettin' scared for nothin'.
去吧，现在就推。不要打翻任何东西。
Go ahead and push, now. Don't knock anything over.
好了。现在，我们把车从下面拿出来。
There we are. Now, we get the dolly out from underneath there.
抬起那一头。把它举起来!
Lift up that end. Lift it up!
加油！加油
Come on, come on.
给你。
There you are.
放下枪，放下枪。我必须做所有的工作吗?
Well, put it down, put it down. Do I have to do all the work?
我会记下的。好吧，把它放下。
I'll get it down. Well, put it down.
去做吧。现在，把它打开。
Go ahead. Now, open it up.
我去拿另一个板条箱。不许顶嘴!
I'm going out and get the other crate. And no back talk!
我只想对你说两个字。那是什么?
I've got just two words to say to you. What is that?
快点回来。
Hurry back.
喂?是的，麦克道格尔先生。
Hello? Yes, Mr. McDougal.
是的，箱子在这里。威尔伯正在打开一个。
Yeah, the crates are here. Wilbur's opening one right now.
一切都好。
Everything's all right.
好的，麦克道格尔先生。再见。
Okay, Mr. McDougal. Goodbye.
小鸡吗?哦,小鸡!
Chick? Oh, Chick!
怎么了?怎么了?
What's the matter? What's the matter?
你关灯了吗?当然不是。
Did you turn out the light? Certainly not.
他们出去了。那又怎样?
They're out. So what?
也许闪电击中了电线什么的。
Maybe the lightning struck the power line or something.
我在这里惹的麻烦更多…没关系，把画布拿下来。
I get in more messes around here... Never mind, take off that canvas.
脱下来?脱下来!
Take it off? Take it off!
嘿，棺材!棺材。
Hey, a coffin! Coffin.
德古拉的徽章。吸血鬼的波峰。
The Dracula crest. Dracula's crest.
我不知道麦克道格尔先生是否希望人们认为德古拉真的在里面。
I wonder if Mr. McDougal expects people to think that Dracula's really in there.
不,不喜欢。请不要。
No, don't. Please don't.
哦，来吧，来吧，来吧。德古拉只是一个传奇人物。
Oh, now come, come, come. Dracula was just a legendary character.
他从未存在过。没有?
He never existed. No?
当然不是。
Certainly not.
把这块帆布折起来。我去拿另一个板条箱。
Fold up this canvas. I'm going out and get the other crate.
如果你需要我，就喊一声。“哦，小鸡!”你明白吗?
If you want me, just holler. Holler, "Oh, Chick!" You understand?
哦,小鸡!你想要什么?
Oh, Chick! What do you want?
什么事耽搁了你?我还没走呢。
What kept you? I haven't left yet.
下次，别花这么长时间。
The next time, don't take so long.
来吧。把这个折起来。让自己忙碌起来。
Come on. Fold this up. Get busy.
“德古拉伯爵睡在这棺材里，但每天晚上日落时他就起床了。”
"Count Dracula sleeps in this coffin, but rises every night at sunset."
奇克说得对。这是可怕的愚蠢的东西。
Chick is right. This is awful silly stuff.
“吸血鬼……”
"Dracula..."
小鸡!小鸡!
Chick! Chick!
现在又怎么了?你还记得那个你说没有的人吗?是吗?
What's the matter now? You know that person you said that there's no such person? Yes?
我想他就在里面，本人。
I think he's in there, in person.
我在看这个牌子，下面这个，"德古拉传奇"
I was reading this sign over here, this one down here, "Dracula's Legend."
突然我听到……
All of a sudden I heard...
那是风。应该给它上油。
That's the wind. It should get oiled.
听着，别读了。
Listen, stop reading this thing.
这是骗麦克道格尔顾客的骗人把戏。
That's a lot of phony baloney to fool McDougal's customers.
现在，把画布折起来。让自己忙碌起来。来吧。
Now, fold up that canvas. Get busy. Come on.
"德古拉可以随心所欲地变成吸血蝙蝠，"在乡间飞来飞去"
"Dracula can change himself at will into a vampire bat, "flying about the countryside."
飞行。
Flying.
喔…
Wooo...
小鸡!
Chick!
听着，你们吵得把死人都吵醒了!
Listen, you're making enough noise to wake up the dead!
我没必要叫醒他。他的了。我看见一只手。
I don't have to wake him up. He's up. I saw a hand.
你看到一只手了吗?在哪里?就在那里。
You saw a hand? Where? Right over there.
让我看看。就在这里。
Let me see it. Right over here.
它在哪里?我看见那里有一只手!
Where is it? I saw a hand there!
你不知道你在说什么!
You don't know what you're talking about!
你们读到这个传说都很兴奋。现在,倾听。听着,威尔伯。
You're all excited reading this legend. Now, listen. Listen, Wilbur.
我知道没有德古拉这个人。
I know there's no such a person as Dracula.
你知道没有德古拉这个人。
You know there's no such a person as Dracula.
但德古拉知道吗?现在，听我说。
But does Dracula know it? Now, listen to me.
麦克道格尔和保险代理人随时会到。
McDougal will be here any minute with the insurance agent.
现在开始工作吧!
Now get to work!
“他靠喝血来维持生命……”
"He keeps himself alive by drinking the blood..."
小鸡。小鸡。
Chick. Chick.
小鸡。
Chick.
小鸡。Ch……
Chick. Ch...
小鸡!
Chick!
听着，这越来越荒唐了。
Now, listen, this is getting to be ridiculous.
什么?什么?
What? What?
你是想告诉我蜡烛动了吗?
Are you trying to tell me that candle moved?
听着，等一下。蜡烛不能移动!这一个做到了。
Look, wait a minute. Candles can't move! This one did.
是的,有。看。盯着点。
Yeah, there. Watch it. Keep your eye on it.
它在动吗?嗯?
Is it moving? Huh?
它不动了，是吗?不是现在。
It's not moving, is it? Not now.
那就动动脑筋吧。让我们把工作做完。
Well, use your brains a little bit. Let's get this job finished.
“他靠喝受害者的血来维持生命。”
"He keeps himself alive by drinking the blood of his victims."
"德古拉伯爵必须在日出前回到棺材里。他……”
"Count Dracula must return to his coffin before sunrise. He..."
小鸡!小鸡!
Chick! Chick!
哦,小鸡!小鸡!
Oh, Chick! Chick!
小鸡!
Chick!
哦，奇克，来吧!来吧!
Oh, Chick, come on! Come on!
好吧，我这就来。
All right, I'm comin'.
来吧，好吗?现在，等一下。又怎么了?
Come on, will ya! Now, wait a minute. What's wrong now?
哦,小鸡!
Oh, Chick!
你要告诉我蜡烛又动了吗?是的,是的。
You gonna tell me that candle moved again? Yeah, yeah.
我告诉过你不要看这个，不是吗?
I told you not to read this, didn't I?
我没办法。我没办法。噢,停下。
I can't help it. I can't help it. Oh, stop.
"德古拉伯爵必须在日出前回到他的棺材里，"白天他只能躺在那里"
"Count Dracula must return to his coffin before sunrise, "where he lies helpless during the day."
那是床铺!这就是我想告诉你的。
That's the bunk! That's what I'm trying to tell ya.
那是他的铺位!
That's his bunk!
到这里来。
Come here.
别这样，奇克。到这里来。来这里!到这儿来!
Oh, don't, Chick. Come here. Come here! Come around here!
到这边来。看里面。
Come over here. Look in there.
现在，你看到什么了吗?
Now, do you see anything?
不。当然不是。
No. Certainly not.
来，帮我打开那个箱子。来吧。
Come on, help me open that crate. Come on.
拜托，快点，好吗?
Come on, get with it, will you please?
你可以…“弗兰肯斯坦的怪物。”来看看这个。到这里来。
You can always... "Frankenstein's Monster. " Get a load of this here. Come here.
"一位名叫弗兰肯斯坦的科学家"把一些老旧的尸体缝合在一起"造出了一个怪物"
"A scientist named Frankenstein made a monster "by sewing together parts of old, dead bodies."
你一定要看那些东西吗?等一下。
Do you have to read that stuff? Wait a minute.
“弗兰肯斯坦用充满电的射击给了怪物永生。
"Frankenstein gave the monster eternal life by shooting it full of electricity.
“有些人说它到现在还没有死，只是处于休眠状态。”
"Some people claim it is not dead even now, just dormant."
谁会傻到相信这种事呢?
Now, who'd be silly enough to believe that?
谁会傻到相信这种事呢?是的。
Who would be silly enough to believe that? Yeah.
我。
Me.
来吧，打开那个箱子。
Come on, open up that crate.
小妞，你听到了吗?
Chick, did you hear that?
是啊，我当然听到你拔指甲了。去做吧。
Yeah, I heard you pulling the nails out, certainly. Go ahead.
拉钉子?
Pulling the nails?
小鸡吗?哦,安静。
Chick? Oh, quiet.
我不想再听你那些愚蠢的问题了。
I don't want to hear any more of your foolish questions.
来吧，把箱子打开，好吗?
Come on, open up the crate, will you?
好了。
There we are.
你说对了。现在抓住它。
You've got it. Now get a hold of it.
把它扔到一边。
Throw it right on the side.
就这样，好吧。现在，来吧，帮我把这个精益求精。
That's it, fine. Now, come on, help me with this excelsior.
来吧，都拿出来。把它从他身上弄下来。
Come on, take it all out. Get it off him.
哇!当心!小妞，盖上它!
Wow! Look out! Chick, cover it up!
怎么了?等一下。把它盖起来!
What's the matter? Wait a minute. Cover it up!
覆盖整个…你怎么了?
Cover the whole... What's the matter with you?
停止!
Stop that!
现在你做到了。
Now you did it.
嘿，你关着灯在里面干什么?
Hey, what are you doing in there with the lights off?
嘿,吉姆!现在我们有麻烦了。
Hey, McDougal! Now we're in trouble.
把头藏起来。快点!快点!
Hide that head. Hurry up! Hurry up!
的主人。
Master.
是的。
Yes.
来了。跟我来。
Come. Follow me.
不要害怕。他不会伤害你的。
Don't be afraid. He won't hurt you.
来了!
Come!
快点。来了。
Hurry up. Come.
这最好是个好主意。
This better be a good one.
怎么了，你怕黑吗?不。
What's the matter, you afraid of the dark? No.
是的，就是这样。就是这样。
Yeah, that's it. That's it.
这是什么?
What is this?
嘿，威尔伯，麦克道戈尔来了。我…你怎么了?
Hey, Wilbur, McDougal is here. I... What's the matter with you?
来吧，振作起来。
Come on, snap out of it.
他们在哪里?我的身体在哪里?
Where are they? Where are my bodies?
身体什么?没有尸体。
What bodies? There were no bodies.
我们打开了两个箱子。我把它拿给威尔伯看。看里面。
We opened both crates. I showed it to Wilbur. Look in there.
如果他们不在这里，那他们在哪里?我不知道。
If they're not here, where are they? I don't know.
一定是偷来的。我们公司在装运前检查了货物。
They must be stolen. My company inspected the contents before they were shipped.
那一定是在路上被偷的。
Then they must've been stolen en route.
你是说，你看见他们了?不，不，不。
You mean, you saw them? No, no, no.
那他们去哪了?我不知道。
Well, then where did they go? I don't know.
如果他们走了，我要我的保险金。我很抱歉。
If they're gone, I want my insurance money. I'm sorry.
在全面调查之前，我的公司是不会付钱的。
My company doesn't pay off until a full investigation.
你听到了吗?如果你不交出尸体，我就报警!
Did you hear that? If you don't produce those bodies, I'm going to call the police!
警察?警察!
Police? Police!
我可以做得更好。警察!
I can do better than that. Police!
我会抓住你的。警察!
I'll get you. Police!
等一下，等一下。来，走，上。
Wait a minute, wait a minute. Come on, go, get on.
把它拿出来。
Let's take it out.
来了!
Come!
晚上好，莫奈医生。
Good evening, Dr. Mornay.
亲爱的伯爵，很高兴再次见到你。
My dear Count, it's so good to see you again.
你看起来比我上次见到你时更迷人了。
And you look more charming than when I saw you last.
请进，德古拉伯爵。谢谢你，桑德拉。
Come in, Count Dracula. Thank you, Sandra.
但我的名字是莱霍斯医生。
But the name is Dr. Lejos.
我可不想吓到你的技术助理。
I wouldn't want to frighten your technical assistant.
史蒂文斯教授?
Professor Stevens?
别担心。他全神贯注地工作。
Don't worry. He's completely engrossed in his work.
再说了，他明天就该走了。
Besides, he should be out of here by tomorrow.
太好了。
Excellent.
是的，只是他问的问题太多了。
Yes, except that he's asking too many questions.
我会处理的。一切都安排好了吗?
I will take care of that. Is everything else arranged?
是的。你把他留在哪儿了?在寒冷中。
Yes. Where did you leave him? In the cold.
我去拿包裹。
I'll get a wrap.
紧张吗，亲爱的?
Nervous, my dear?
这是一件有风险的事。
This is risky business.
不像你的那些奇怪的行动那么冒险，那些行动引起了欧洲警方的兴趣。但利润要高得多。
Not as risky as those curious operations of yours, that so intrigued the European police. Yet much more profitable.
把怪物还给我，你就能得到你想要的一切。
Restore the monster for me, and you shall have anything you wish.
那样的话，我们最好尽快出发。
In that case, we better start as soon as possible.
让他处于这种虚弱的状态是很危险的。
It's dangerous to leave him in this weakened condition.
你掌握了弗兰肯斯坦博士的笔记本了吗?
Have you mastered Dr. Frankenstein's notebook?
让我再拿起手术刀，你就会明白了。
Let me get my hand on a scalpel again and you shall see.
关于大脑呢?
And about the brain?
我不想重复弗兰肯斯坦的错误，复活一个恶毒的，难以控制的畜生。
I don't want to repeat Frankenstein's mistake, and revive a vicious, unmanageable brute.
这一次怪物必须没有自己的意志。
This time the monster must have no will of his own.
没有魔鬼般的智力来对抗他的主人。
No fiendish intellect to oppose his master.
好了，我亲爱的伯爵，我相信我已经超出了您的期望。
There, my dear Count, I believe I have exceeded your fondest wishes.
我为怪物选择的新大脑非常简单，非常柔韧，它会像训练有素的狗一样服从你。
The new brain I've chosen for the monster is so simple, so pliable, he will obey you like a trained dog.
很好。有多快呢?
Good. How soon?
后天。威尔伯要带我去参加化装舞会。
The day after tomorrow. Wilbur was taking me to a masquerade ball.
但我肯定他更愿意在家里安静地度过一个晚上。
But I'm sure he'd prefer to spend a quiet evening at home.
把他带过来。
Bring him through here.
我告诉你，奇克，我看到了我看到的一切!
I tell you, Chick, I saw what I saw when I saw it!
保持安静!你在胡言乱语说死人都走了!
Keep quiet! You babbling about dead people walking away!
所以我们才被抓起来关进监狱。
That's why we were arrested and thrown in jail.
你知不知道我们在监狱里待了一整天一夜?
Do you realize that we've spent a whole day and night in jail?
如果不是有个女人救了我们，我们现在还在那里。
And we'd still be there if some dame hadn't've bailed us out.
小妞，别叫桑德拉娘娘腔了!
Chick, now stop calling Sandra a dame!
我告诉你，他们就在那里。
And I'm tellin' ya, they were there.
噢,停下。两个。
Oh, stop. Two of 'em.
其中一个大约有八英尺高。
One of 'em was about eight foot tall.
好高啊!他像这样走路。
Way up there! And he walked like this.
就像这样。
Just like that.
这就是他走路的方式。阻止它。
Now, that's the way he walked. Stop it.
你不相信吗?当然不!
You don't believe that? Certainly not!
嗯，我看到了。
Well, I saw it.
另一个是这样的。
And the other one, he went like this.
他越靠越近。
And he kept gettin' closer and closer.
他的眼睛像火球一样。
He had eyes that were balls of fire.
他目不转睛地盯着我。
He kept staring, eye to eye.
眼睛对眼睛!盯着!
Eye to eye! Staring!
我这辈子从没见过这样的东西。
I never saw anything like it in my life.
相信我，奇克，我当时吓死你了。
Believe me, Chick, when I tell you I was scared to death.
真的。我真的很害怕，奇克。
Really I was. I was really scared, Chick.
怎么了?小鸡吗?
What's the matter? Chick?
我做了什么?
What did I do?
嘿，奇克，我不喜欢你那样。来吧，就像以前一样。
Hey, Chick, I don't like you like that. Come on, be just like you used to be.
滚开!好啊! !我很高兴。
Go away with it! Attaboy! I'm happy.
这跟你以前一样。
That's just like you used to be.
好的。现在，别胡说了!所有的一切。
All right. Now, stop this nonsense! All of it.
你是威尔伯·格雷?是的,先生。
You're Wilbur Grey? Yes, sir.
那你一定是奇克·杨。那又怎样?
Then you must be Chick Young. So what?
我是劳伦斯·塔尔博特。我在城里到处找你。
I'm Lawrence Talbot. I've been looking all over town for you.
你不用找太远。我们在监狱里。是的，我知道。
You didn't have to look far. We were in jail. Yes, I know.
你看，是我打电话叫你不要送尸体的。
You see, I'm the one who telephoned you not to deliver those bodies.
我知道他们还活着!
I knew they were alive!
你在这啊，你以为我在胡思乱想吗?
There you are, so you thought I was imagining things, huh?
当我告诉你一个八英尺高的家伙，像这样走路，腿僵硬，然后另一个像这样。
When I told you about the fellow that was eight-foot tall, and walking like this with the stiff legs, and then the other fellow with this here.
等等!等一下。你疯了，这个疯子也是!
Wait! Wait a minute. You're crazy, and so is this screwball!
听着，小子，我也有自己的麻烦。比你想象的还要糟糕。
Look, bub, I have my own troubles. Worse than you think.
我从欧洲一路跟随德古拉，因为我相信他会试图复活弗兰肯斯坦怪物。
I followed Dracula all the way from Europe, because I believe that he's going to try and revive the Frankenstein monster.
我们必须在他做出这种事之前找到他并摧毁他!
We must find him and destroy him before he can do this!
等一下，你为什么不去找警察，告诉他们你知道德古拉和怪物的故事。
Wait a minute, why don't you go down to the police, tell them you know the story about Dracula and the Monster.
他们会很感兴趣的。我不能那么做。
They'd be very interested. I can't do that.
因为那样我就得告诉他们我是谁…为什么我知道我所知道的。
Because then I'd have to tell them who I am and... Why I know what I know.
很快……不久月亮就要升起来了。
Soon... Soon the moon will rise.
我没时间解释了。
I haven't time to explain.
我订了对门的房间。这是钥匙。把我锁起来!
I've taken the room across the hall. Here's the key. Lock me in!
把你锁起来?是的,请。快点!
Lock you in? Yes, please. Hurry!
这很傻，但我会做的。
It's silly, but I'll do it.
他也很害怕。
He's scared too.
记住，不管你听到了什么，发生了什么，别让我出去!
Remember, no matter what you hear or what happens, don't let me out!
“把我锁起来。”那家伙比你更变态。
"Lock me in." That guy is screwier than you are.
他不是。他是个好人。
He is not. He's a nice man.
他只是担心警察抓到他因为他知道他们还活着。
He's just worried about the police getting him because he knows they're alive.
我要去睡觉了。嗯…嘿，他忘带包了。
I'm going to bed. Well... Hey, he forgot his bag.
塔尔博特先生，你忘记拿握把了。
Mr. Talbot, you forgot your grip.
塔尔博特先生吗?
Mr. Talbot?
他是怎么逃出去的?
Now, how'd he get out of here?
嗯。
Hmm.
我会给他留张便条的。
I'll leave him a note.
“我把你的包落在卧室了。
"I left your bag in the bedroom.
“威尔伯。”
"Wilbur."
我不知道他有没有数过这些。
I wonder if he counted these.
他可能已经。
He might've.
也许他没有。
Maybe he didn't.
嗯。
Hmm.
跟我做生意的保险公司还不错，却被两个白痴耍了!
A fine insurance company I'm doing business with, outsmarted by a couple of morons!
那两个骗子出狱了。保释!
Those two crooks got out of jail. On bail!
我们知道，麦克道格尔先生，但你看我们…事实上，是我安排的。你吗?你是谁?
We know that, Mr. McDougal, but you see we... In fact, I arranged it. You? Who are you?
这位是雷蒙德小姐，总公司的调查员。
This is Miss Raymond, an investigator from the home office.
我的工作是，麦克道格尔先生，找到那些丢失的展品。
It's my job, Mr. McDougal, to find those missing exhibits.
我相信我能说服这个胖乎乎的小家伙带我找到他们。
I'm quite sure I can persuade the chubby little fellow to lead me right to them.
当然，在监狱里我也不能很好地说服他。
Naturally, I couldn't persuade him very well in jail.
威尔伯,谢谢!我整晚都做噩梦!
Wilbur, please! I've had nightmares all night long!
我不想再听到尸体的事了。
I don't want to hear any more about dead bodies.
我看到了我看到的一切。
I saw what I saw when I saw it.
好吧。
All right.
天啊，见到你真高兴。你能过去和那个人谈谈吗?
Boy, am I glad to see you. Will you go over and talk to that guy?
桑德拉!威尔伯，亲爱的，我听说发生了什么事。
Sandra! Wilbur darling, I heard what happened.
这是很糟糕的。他们不能把我的小威尔伯关进监狱。
That's awful. They can't put my little Wilbur in jail.
他们不能，但他们做了。
They can't, but they did.
桑德拉，我想谢谢你保释我们出来。
Sandra, I wanna thank you for bailing us out.
我吗?我今天早上才知道。
I? I only learned about it this morning.
警察没告诉你是一位女士保释了我们吗?
Well, didn't the policeman tell you that a lady bailed us out?
他做到了。
He did.
威尔伯，亲爱的，你没有对你的桑德拉不忠吧?
Wilbur, pet, you haven't been untrue to your Sandra?
桑德拉，你怎么能当着我的面这么说?
Sandra, how can you look me in the face and say that?
你怎么能直视他的脸，就这样?
How can you look him in the face, period?
我只是来提醒你今晚化装舞会的事。
I only came by to remind you about the masquerade ball tonight.
我正准备去拿我的戏服。
I was just getting ready to pick up my costume.
早点来接我吧，亲爱的。关于日落。
Come by for me early, dearest. About sunset.
一个人。再见。
Alone. Goodbye.
我想知道的是，他有什么是我没有的?
What I'd like to know is, what has he got that I haven't got?
一个大脑。
A brain.
一个大脑。我想知道它在哪里。
A brain. I'd like to know where it is.
哦。她忘了和我吻别。
Oh. She forgot to kiss me goodbye.
你是谁?她的……她的……她是美丽的。
Now, who is this? She's... She's... She's beautiful.
琼·雷蒙德报道。她是琼·雷蒙德。
I'm Joan Raymond. She's Joan Raymond.
是我安排你出狱的。
I'm the girl who arranged your release from jail.
那你为什么要放我们走?
Well, why should you want to spring us?
你相信一见钟情吗?
Do you believe in love at first sight?
好!既然你这么说，我…这就是我的遭遇。
Well! As long as you put it that way, I... That's what happened to me.
威尔伯,亲爱的!
Wilbur, darling!
雷蒙德小姐，你第一次有这种疯狂的感觉是什么时候?
Miss Raymond, when did this mad feeling first come over you?
我在行李室看到你的那一刻。
The instant I saw you in the baggage room.
那时我就知道我想和你共度城里的每一分钟。
I knew then that I wanted to spend every single minute that I'm in town with you.
你做了吗?
You did?
我们今晚做什么?
What are we doing tonight?
他要去参加化装舞会。
He's going to a masquerade ball.
但我什么都没做。
But I'm not doing anything.
那样的话，你会很寂寞的。嗯,自然……威尔伯，亲爱的，我好久没参加化妆舞会了。
In that case, you'll be awfully lonesome. Well, naturally... Wilbur darling, I haven't been to a masquerade ball in ages.
我只是希望你会问我。
I was just hoping you'd ask me.
威尔伯!到这里来。
Wilbur! Come here.
雷蒙德小姐，能失陪一下吗?
Miss Raymond, will you excuse me?
噢，你这个不可抗拒的孩子!
Oh, you irresistible boy!
你需要我吗?是的，我需要你。到这边来。
Do you want me? Yes, I want you. Come over here.
我只是想在灯光下好好看看你。
I just wanted to get a good look at you in the light.
我还是不明白。嫉妒?
I still don't get it. Jealous?
威尔伯，我得出去买套服装。
Wilbur, I'll have to go out and get a costume.
这是有趣的。我也正要走呢。
That's funny. I was just going, too.
我先下楼去房间拿点东西，然后在大厅见你。
I'll go down to my room and pick up a couple things and meet you in the lobby.
好的。在大厅。
All right. In the lobby.
我去拿帽子和外套。我马上就来。
I'll get my hat and coat. I'll be right with you.
打扰一下。看。
Excuse me. Look.
现在你有两个约会了。桑德拉呢，你这个重婚者?
Now you've got two dates. What about Sandra, you bigamist?
桑德拉?我不知道。琼真可爱。
Sandra? I don't know. Joan is awful cute.
好吧，你负责琼，我负责桑德拉。哦，桑德拉派我来的。
All right, you take Joan, I'll take Sandra. Oh, Sandra sends me.
好吧，那我带琼去。琼也派我来的。
Well, then I'll take Joan. Joan sends me too.
听着，你这个被锯掉的罗密欧，过一会儿，我就派你去!
Now, listen, you sawed-off Romeo, in a minute, I'll send you!
你对我一点吸引力都没有。
You don't even appeal to me.
听着，威尔伯，我们一直是好朋友，不是吗?
Look, Wilbur, we've always been pals, haven't we?
哦,是的。我们一直都是一样的分享，不是吗?嗯哼。
Oh, yes. We've always shared, and shared alike, haven't we? Mm-hmm.
好吧，听着，让我们讲道理。来吧。
Well, now, look, let's be reasonable. Come on.
我一直和你分享的。你有!
I've always shared with you. That you have!
如果我有两支烟，我会给你一支。这是正确的。
If I had two cigarettes, I'd give you one. That's right.
如果我有两双鞋，我会给你一双。
And if I had two pair of shoes, I'd give you a pair.
我不知道吗?如果我有两个女儿…好吗?
Don't I know that? And if I have two girls... Well?
你为什么不点上那根烟，穿上这双鞋，自己去散个步呢?
Why don't you light that cigarette, put on those shoes and take a walk for yourself?
这就是我要做的，但和你一起。
That's what I'm going to do, but with you.
这把钥匙不合适。这是……托尔伯特的关键。
This key don't fit. This is... Talbot's key.
嘿，我们忘了他了。
Hey, we forgot about him.
天哪，他昨晚一定喝得烂醉如泥!
Boy, what a bender he must've been on last night!
塔尔博特先生。塔尔博特先生!
Hey, Mr. Talbot. Mr. Talbot!
我还以为你是个好人呢。看看你自己。
And I thought you were such a nice man, too. Look at yourself.
你真是一团糟!昨晚……我又经历了一次可怕的经历。
You're a mess! Last night... I went through another of my horrible experiences.
多年前我被狼人咬了。
Years ago I was bitten by a werewolf.
从那时起，每当满月升起，我自己也会变成狼。
Ever since, when the full moon rises, I turn into a wolf myself.
哦，伙计，没关系。
Oh, pal, that's all right.
我自己也算是狼人。我还以为…我以为只有你会相信我，以为只有你知道我说的是实话。
I'm sort of a wolf myself. And here I thought... I thought that you were the only one that would believe me, that you were the one that knew that I spoke the truth.
你见过活死人。嗯哼。
You have seen the living dead. Mm-hmm.
我大老远从欧洲赶来，因为德古拉和怪物必须被消灭。
I came all the way from Europe, because Dracula and the Monster must be destroyed.
我们必须一起找到他们!
Together we must find them!
哦，不，现在，等一下。我们不要再来一遍了。
Oh no, now, wait a minute. Let's not start that all over again.
我不能去。我有个约会。事实上，我有两个约会。
I can't go. I've got a date. In fact, I've got two dates.
但你和我是命中注定的约会。
But you and I have a date with destiny.
让奇克跟着命运走吧。
Let Chick go with destiny.
好吗?
Won't you please?
你们两个孩子待在这里。我要上去叫桑德拉。
You two kids stay here. I'm going up and get Sandra.
她也是我的。
She's mine too.
请稍等一下。威尔伯!
Pardon me just a minute. Wilbur!
你看，你有琼和桑德拉。
Now, look, you've got Joan and Sandra.
你有两个女儿!那上周的两个女孩呢?
You've got two girls! How about the two girls we had last week?
我们不要谈这个了。
Let's not talk about that.
你来不了。我没有踢。
You got no kick comin'. I'm not kicking.
你有一个最好看的。那又怎样?
You had the best lookin' one. So what?
你的有牙齿。看，威尔伯，你的也有牙齿。
Yours had teeth. Look, Wilbur, yours had teeth too.
你看到那颗牙了吗?是的，我碰巧看到了。
Did you see that tooth? Yes, I happened to see it.
我的桥上有很多桥，每次我吻她都要付过路费。
Mine had so much bridgework, every time I kissed her I had to pay toll.
有什么用?
What's the use?
威尔伯，我们不能一起去吗?
Wilbur, can't we both go along, too?
是的，我的爱人。这是西班牙语。这是法语。
Yes, mon amour. That's Spanish. That's French.
你觉得怎么样?我也会说法语。哦，你这个可爱的小恶魔!
How do you like that? I speak French too. Oh, you cute little devil!
阻止这种情况的发生。
Stop that.
来吧，带路。来吧。
Come on, lead the way. Come on.
你好。你好。
Hello. Hello.
桑德拉在吗?谁?
Is Sandra in? Who?
桑德拉。你是说莫奈医生?
Sandra. You mean, Dr. Mornay?
好吧，如果她是那样的人，我就是医生要的。
Well, if that's what she is, I'm just what the doctor ordered.
进来。谢谢你！
Come in. Thank you.
我以为桑德拉是你的女伴。
I thought this Sandra was your date.
还是我们都是一起来兜风的?不,不。
Or did we both come along for the ride? No, no.
也许我应该介绍一下我自己。我是史蒂文斯教授。
Perhaps I should introduce myself. I'm Professor Stevens.
这是雷蒙德小姐，这是威尔伯·格雷，我是奇克·杨。
This is Miss Raymond, This is Wilbur Grey, and I'm Chick Young.
你好，雷蒙德小姐。你好!
How do you do, Miss Raymond? How do you do?
我还有工作要完成，不过应该花不了几分钟。
I have work to finish, but it shouldn't take more than a few minutes.
你在图书馆等我，我马上下来。
If you'll wait in the library, I'll be right down.
只是为了记录清楚。我们是来接桑德拉的。
Just to keep the records clear. We're here to pick up Sandra.
当然可以。我肯定她就在附近。
Of course. I'm sure she's around somewhere.
威尔伯!
Wilbur!
桑德拉,你好。
Sandra, hello.
那个女孩，她是谁?
That girl, who is she?
她是奇克的女伴。她要和我们一起去化装舞会。
She's Chick's date. She's going to the masquerade with us.
但我告诉过你一个人来。我们得把它们处理掉。
But I told you to come here alone. We'll have to get rid of them.
我得解雇一个人。
I'll have to get rid of somebody.
你好,桑德拉。你好,女孩。
Hello, Sandra. Hello, Chick.
琼，这是桑德拉。桑德拉,琼。
Joan, this is Sandra. Sandra, Joan.
你这地方真不错，医生。谁告诉你我是医生的?
Nice place you have here, Doctor. Who told you I was a doctor?
就是那个应门的年轻人。
Why, the young man who answered the door.
哦，史蒂文斯教授。
Oh, Professor Stevens.
你知道，我在度假，而且是隐姓埋名地旅行。
I'm on a vacation, you see, and traveling incognito.
你在这里做什么?同样的事情。
What are you doing here? Same thing.
我们走吧?等我穿上戏服就走。
Shall we get going? Just as soon as I put on my costume.
你想上个妆吗?我很乐意。
Would you like to powder your nose? I'd love to.
我马上回来，威尔伯。
I'll be right back, Wilbur.
我也马上回来，威尔伯。
I'll be right back, too, Wilbur.
Toodle-oo !
Toodle-oo!
小妞，每个人都有惹上麻烦的时候。
Chick, there's a time in everyone's life when they get in trouble.
我现在是一团糟。怎么了?
I'm in a mess of it right now. Now, what's wrong?
我有两个女儿。你知道有句老话吗?
I've got two girls. You know the old saying?
“每样东西都成三。”
"Everything comes in threes."
现在，假如第三个女孩爱上了你呢?
Now, suppose a third girl should fall in love with you?
她叫什么名字?我们就说她叫玛丽。
What's her name? We'll say her name is Mary.
她漂亮吗?美丽。
Is she pretty? Beautiful.
很自然地，她必须这么做。
Naturally, she'd have to be.
现在你有了玛丽，琼和桑德拉。
Now you have Mary, you have Joan and you have Sandra.
所以，为了向你证明我是你的朋友，你的知心朋友，我将从你手上带走一个女孩。
So, to prove to you that I'm your pal, your bosom friend, I'll take one of the girls off your hands.
小妞，你才是我所谓的真正的朋友，没事的。
Chick, you're what I call a real pal. It's all right.
你带玛丽去。
You take Mary.
我们最好接电话。他们都在楼上。
We better answer that phone. They're all upstairs.
你好。喂?
Hello. Hello?
Lejos医生在吗?
Is Dr. Lejos there?
请稍等。有人想了解一个叫莱霍斯的医生。
Just a minute. Somebody wants to know about a Dr. Lejos.
我不认识他。
I don't know him.
喂?您是哪位?这是威尔伯·格雷。
Hello? Who is this speaking? This is Wilbur Grey.
我想我听出你的声音了。
I thought I recognized your voice.
我是塔尔博特。
This is Talbot speaking.
听。我刚得到一条关于德古拉和怪物的线索。
Listen. I just got a line on Dracula and the Monster.
有个叫莱霍斯的医生收到了很多电子设备，都是唤醒怪物所需的那种。
A certain Dr. Lejos has been receiving a lot of electrical equipment, just the type necessary to revive the Monster.
那又怎样?我在一个遥远的岛上。
So what? I'm way out on an island.
我有我自己的问题。是的，但是听着。
I've got my own problems. Yes, but listen.
我相信你现在就在德古拉的房子里。
I believe you're in the house of Dracula right now.
你可以找到怪物，而我…喂?
You can find the Monster, and I'll... Hello?
威尔伯!
Wilbur!
来这里!
Come here!
小妞，你不知道你在做什么，孩子!
Chick, you don't know what you're doin', son!
你怎么了?安静。到这里来。
What's the matter with you? Quiet. Come here.
你没有挂电话。让他把电话挂了。
You didn't hang up the phone. Let him hang up the phone.
谁?吸血鬼。
Who? Dracula.
德古拉和怪物住在这里。
Dracula and the Monster live here.
等一下。别再这样了。谁告诉你的?
Wait a minute. Don't start that again. Who told you that?
托尔伯特。他还说我们要搜查那个地方。
Talbot. He also said that we got to search the place.
到这里来。
Come here.
到这边来。
Come over here.
听着，塔尔博特，够了。现在，威尔伯害怕……喂?喂?他走了。我也是。
Now, listen, Talbot, enough is enough. Now, Wilbur's scared to... Hello? Hello? He's gone. So am I.
不，你不需要。到这里来。我要彻底解决这件事。
No, you don't. Come here. I'm gonna settle this thing once and for all.
我们要搜查这个地方。奇克，日落刚过，如果德古拉来了，他肯定想吃早餐。
We'll search this place. Look, Chick, it's a little past sunset, and if Dracula is here, he's gonna be wanting breakfast.
我比你胖，我不会死的!
And I'm fatter than you, and it ain't gonna be me!
现在，稍等一下。请稍等。不会是我!
Now, just a minute. Just a minute. It ain't gonna be me!
等一下，我要证明你和塔尔博特有多疯狂。
Wait a minute, I'm gonna prove just how crazy both you and Talbot really are.
我们从地下室开始搜这个地方。
We'll search this place, right from the basement.
看,小鸡。什么?
Look, Chick. What?
我们会搜索的。这是更多…你和我在一起。这才像话。
We'll search it. That's more... You and I together. Now we're talkin'.
好啊!。你搜地下室，我去外面搜。
Attaboy. You search the basement, I'll search outside.
哦，不，你没有!好吧，我去外面找，你去地下室找。
Oh, no, you don't! All right, then, I'll search on outside, and you search the basement.
这是不同的。
That's different.
-成功了!-来吧!
- It worked! - Come on!
现在，让我们看看这里。
Now, let's look around here.
下面有几扇门。
There's some doors down there.
你觉得我们该告诉桑德拉我们要去哪吗?
You think we oughta tell Sandra where we're goin'?
当然不是。
Certainly not.
你看那边。
You look over there.
好吗?杂物室。
Well? Broom closet.
什么?
What?
杂物室吗?看出来。
Broom closet? Look out.
来吧。
Come on.
杂物室吗?
Broom closet?
来吧!等我一下。
Come on! Wait for me.
来吧。
Come on.
哦!
Oh!
小鸡!打开!
Chick! Open!
哇!
Whoa!
小鸡!来吧。小鸡!
Chick! Come on. Chick!
小鸡!你从下面往里面搜。嘘。
Chick! You search down there and on the inside. Shh.
停!这是事实。到这里来。
Stop! It's the truth. Come here.
我所做的就是这样。
All I did was like this.
现在，奇克，我告诉你，到那边去。
Now, Chick, I tell you, right over there.
他们在哪里?他们在哪里?
Where are they? Where are they?
它们在里面。它们在里面。现在,倾听。
They're in there. They're in there. Now, listen.
等一下。我要四处看看。你去吧。
Wait a minute. I'm gonna look around. You go ahead.
如果我找不到人，我就打烂你的耳朵。
If I don't find anybody, I'm gonna beat your ears off.
我告诉你，奇克。诚实的。好吧，在这儿等着。
I'm telling you, Chick. Honest. Well, wait here.
他们在那边。哦,不。我再也不会靠近那个地方了。
They're over there. Oh, no. I ain't goin' near that place anymore.
哇!噢!
Whoa! Ooh!
芝麻开门!芝麻开门!
Open sesame! Open sesame!
他们在哪里?他们一定在里面。
Well, where are they? They must be in there.
噢,停下。听着，威尔伯，我对你这些愚蠢的胡言乱语感到厌烦。
Oh, stop. Now, listen Wilbur, I'm getting sick and tired of this silly nonsense of yours.
-有个家伙…-不，不。
- Some guy going around... - No, no.
另一个家伙…不,不!
Another guy goin'... No, no!
只有一个人…大……另一个，不是这样，像这样。
The one guy goes... The big... And the other guy, not like that, like this.
是的。好，好，好。把手放下。
Yeah. All right, all right, all right. Put your hands down.
走吧，姑娘们在楼上等我们呢。来吧。
Come on, the girls are waiting for us upstairs. Come on.
你认识威尔伯很久了吗?是的，我们是老朋友了。
Have you known Wilbur long? Yes, we're old friends.
你要等很久吗?只要几分钟。
Will you be long? Just a few minutes.
雷蒙德小姐吗?是吗?
Miss Raymond? Yes?
我准备好了。我们走吧?
I'm ready. Shall we go?
当然。
Of course.
这是你的钱包，亲爱的。谢谢你！
Here's your purse, dear. Thank you.
谁尖叫?你做的!
Who screamed? You did!
我做了吗?
I did?
听着，威尔伯，如果你不停止幻想这些疯狂的事情，我就带你去看医生，给你检查一下。
Now, listen, Wilbur, if you don't stop imagining these crazy things, I'll take you to a doctor to have you examined.
但我告诉你，我看到他们了。当我看到我所看到的，我真的看到了。这是所有。
But I'm telling you, I saw them. And when I see what I see, I saw it. That's all.
因为塔尔博特先生也看到了。
Because Mr. Talbot, same way, he saw it too.
托尔伯特!他疯了。你们两个都疯了!
Talbot! He's crazy. You're both crazy!
桑德拉。
Sandra.
桑德拉，我得告诉你。我在楼下的地下室。
Sandra, I've just gotta tell you. I was downstairs in the basement.
地下室吗?你在下面做什么?
Basement? And what were you doing down there?
我打开门。他打开门，从楼梯上摔了下来。
I opened the door. He opened the door, and fell down the stairs.
撒谎者。多么粗心啊!
Fibber. How careless!
你要小心!那样会害死人的!
You should be careful! A person can get killed that way!
希望你没被打扰，莱霍斯医生。
I hope you weren't disturbed, Dr. Lejos.
完全没问题，亲爱的。我作介绍。
It's perfectly all right, my dear. Introduce me.
这是雷蒙德小姐。年轻的先生。
This is Miss Raymond. Mr. Young.
这是威尔伯。
And this is Wilbur.
啊,威尔伯!为什么!
Ah, Wilbur! Why!
我听说了很多关于你的事，我觉得我们好像已经见过一样。
I heard so much about you, I feel as if we have already met.
我得说，亲爱的，我非常赞同你的选择。
And I must say, my dear, I approve very highly of your choice.
我们今天需要的是年轻的血液。
What we need today is young blood.
和大脑!
And brains!
哦，别害羞。来了。
Oh, don't be bashful. Come.
你好，Lejos医生。我一整天都在找你。
Hello, Dr. Lejos. I've been looking for you all day.
你知道吗，每次我问莫内医生那些设备要做什么，她都让我问你。
You know, every time I ask Dr. Mornay what that equipment is going to be used for, she says to ask you.
当然。
Of course.
我不是听说你要参加化装舞会吗?
Didn't I hear that you were going to masquerade ball?
是的，我们的服装在船上。哦，你们这些年轻人!
Yes, we have our costumes out in the boat. Oh, you young people!
趁生命还在，充分利用它。
Making the most of life, while it lasts.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
教授，你工作很努力很好。
Professor, you've worked hard and well.
你为什么不加入他们，把你的问题留到明天再问?
Why don't you join them, and save your questions until tomorrow?
一般情况下我会说不，但是……如果你不介意的话?
Under ordinary circumstances I'd say no, but... If you don't mind?
一点也不。很好。我去拿外套。
Not at all. Good. I'll get my coat.
当然，这对一艘船来说太多了。
Of course that would make too many for one boat.
但如果教授和这位女士和这位先生继续，当然可以。
But if the professor and this lady and gentleman go on ahead, sure.
威尔伯和莫内医生可以……恐怕不行。
Wilbur and Dr. Mornay can... I'm afraid I can't.
怎么了?
What's the matter?
我突然头痛欲裂。
I've suddenly developed a splitting headache.
对不起，威尔伯，你得一个人走了。
I'm sorry, Wilbur, but you'll have to go without me.
胡说!它来的快，去的也快。
Nonsense! It will pass as quickly as it came.
没用的，医生。我得马上去睡觉了。
It's no use, Doctor. I shall have to go directly to bed.
原谅我。奇克，你的女伴走了。
Pardon me. Well, Chick, there goes your date.
那么，这到底是怎么回事?
Now then, what was that all about?
这东西太危险了。这个女孩是一名保险调查员。
This thing is too dangerous. The girl is an insurance investigator.
史蒂文斯问的问题太多了。
Stevens is asking too many questions.
威尔伯在地下室有什么阴谋。
And Wilbur was up to something in the basement.
我想我们应该等等。
I think we ought to wait.
会危及行动的成功吗?从来没有!
And jeopardize the success of the operation? Never!
我必须警告你，亲爱的桑德拉，我习惯于让人服从我的命令，尤其是那些被悬赏的女人。
I must warn you, my dear Sandra, I am accustomed to having my orders obeyed, especially by women with a price on their heads.
别想吓我，德古拉伯爵。
Don't try to scare me, Count Dracula.
在这里。弗兰肯斯坦博士的《生与死的秘密》
Here. The Secrets of Life and Death by Dr. Frankenstein.
记住它们。如果你这么急的话，自己做手术。
Memorize them. Operate yourself, if you're in such a hurry.
我还有别的办法能保证你的合作。
I have other ways of securing your cooperation.
你在浪费时间。我的意志和你的一样坚强。
You're wasting your time. My will is as strong as yours.
你确定吗?
Are you sure?
看着我的眼睛。
Look into my eyes.
看！
Look!
更深。
Deeper.
告诉我你看到了什么。
Tell me what you see.
琼，奇克和我去储物柜换戏服。
Joan, Chick and I are gonna go into the lockers and change into our costumes.
走吧，教授。我们在舞池见。
Come on, Professor. We'll meet you on the dance floor.
好的。
Okay.
我做了什么?你是什么意思?
What did I do? What do you mean?
他在和我女朋友跳舞!那又怎样?
He's dancing with my girl! So what?
我要让她看看!
I'll show her!
我恋爱了…来吧。把那些捆起来!好的。
I'm in love... Come on. Pick up those bundles! Okay.
我们穿衣服吧。来吧。
Let's get dressed. Come on.
原来是你!啊，他认识我!
So, it's you! Ah, he knows me!
麦克道戈尔!听着，胖子，我的展品呢?
McDougal! Listen, fat boy, where are my exhibits?
现在，你离他远点!
Now, you leave him alone!
除非他告诉我展品在哪里。
Not until he tells me where those exhibits are.
他们在哪里?他们在哪里?
Where are they? Where are they?
麦克道格尔，现在我们抓到你了。
McDougal, now we've got it on you.
你把我们关进了监狱。我们会以人身攻击罪逮捕你。
You put us in jail. Now, we'll have you arrested for assault and battery.
去吧，看看会有什么好处。你没有目击证人。
Go ahead and see what good it'll do ya. You haven't got a witness.
我是证人!我的话和你的话一样可靠!
I'm a witness! My word's as good as yours!
你的话比他的好。你别管这事。
Your word is better than his. You keep outta this.
我去找个证人。帮我个忙，好吗，伙计?
I'll get a witness. Do me a favor, will you, fella?
你会看这个吗?我需要一个证人。
Will you watch this? I need a witness.
去做吧。我想看你再做一次。
Go ahead. I'd like to see you do it again.
你看到了吗?
Did you see it?
我很抱歉。我什么也看不见。
I'm sorry. I couldn't see a thing.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
你见过奇克·杨和威尔伯·格雷吗?
Have you seen Chick Young or Wilbur Grey?
见过他们吗?我甚至不认识他们。
Seen them? I don't even know them.
我得知道他们在岛上发现了什么。
I've got to know what they found on that island.
小鸡!威尔伯!你发现了什么?
Chick! Wilbur! What did you find?
我说得对吗?不。
Was I right? No.
我希望你不要再把那些想法灌输给这孩子。
And I wish you'd stop trying to put those ideas in this boy's head.
他不习惯。去把衣服穿上，威尔伯。
He's not used to them. Go put your things on, Wilbur.
你见过莱霍斯医生吗?是的。
Did you meet Dr. Lejos? Yes.
他长什么样子?高大，贵族，眼神恍惚?
What did he look like? Tall, aristocratic, a faraway look in his eye?
我只知道他让我们出去找点乐子。
All I know is he told us to go out and have some fun.
为什么不呢?
Why don't you?
难道我不能让你相信德古拉是个非常危险的人吗?
Can't I convince you that Dracula is a very dangerous person?
你和威尔伯只是想吓唬我。好吧，这行不通!
You and Wilbur are just trying to scare me. Well, it won't work!
我吓到你了。
I scared ya.
我吓到你了，你个大娘娘腔。
I scared ya, you big sissy.
这是你的面具。我的吗?
This is your mask over there. Mine?
哦，不，不。请不要穿那个。怎么了?
Oh, no, no. Please don't wear that. What's the matter?
我知道你会觉得我疯了，但是…半小时后月亮就会升起，我就会变成狼。
I know you'll think I'm crazy, but... In a half an hour the moon will rise and I'll turn into a wolf.
你和其他两千万男人。听!
You and 20 million other guys. Listen!
我可能会把你撕成碎片!
I might tear you limb from limb!
严重吗?他会杀了你的!
Is that serious? He'll murder ya!
这是严重的。
That's serious.
如果你把我锁在房间里就不会了。
It won't be if you'll just take me and lock me in my room.
请。哦，好吧。
Please. Oh, all right.
你为什么不给自己雇个管理员呢?
Why don't you hire yourself a keeper?
来吧。
Come on.
嘿!
Hey!
看。哦，桑德拉来了。
Look. Oh, Sandra's coming.
都清楚了吗?我会照顾好那女孩的。
Is it all clear? I will take care of the girl.
你把威尔伯带回城堡。
And you'll take Wilbur back to the castle.
明白吗?是的,主人。
Understand? Yes, Master.
桑德拉，你看起来…所以…我们又见面了，德古拉伯爵。
Sandra, you look... So... We meet again, Count Dracula.
吸血鬼吗?是的。他就是这么说你的。
Dracula? Yes. That's who he says you are.
哦，也许是我的服装。不，塔尔博特认为你是真的。
Oh, my costume perhaps. No, Talbot here thinks you're the real thing.
啊哈。就像麦克道格尔的恐怖之屋。
Uh-huh. Right out of McDougal's House of Horrors.
多么奇怪的幻觉啊。
What an odd hallucination.
但人类的思想常常被奇怪的情结所点燃。
But the human mind is often inflamed with strange complexes.
我建议你去咨询你的医生，塔尔博特先生。
I suggest you consult your physician, Mr. Talbot.
请带他一起走。
And take him along with you, please.
好吧，原来是这样!
Well, so there you are!
我很高兴看到你康复了。
I'm glad to see you've recovered.
没想到会在这里见到你，医生。桑德拉一定要我来。
I didn't expect to see you here, Doctor. Sandra insisted I come.
此外，我需要放松一下。
Besides, I need a little relaxation.
雷蒙德小姐，能请您跳支舞吗?
Miss Raymond, would you honor me with a dance?
不。不!
No. No!
我警告你。他是德古拉伯爵!
I warn you. He is Count Dracula!
多么有趣。告诉我更多。
How interesting. Tell me more.
不，让我告诉你…当我们跳舞的时候。
No, let me tell you... While we dance.
对不起，塔尔博特先生。
Pardon me, Mr. Talbot.
桑德拉，你还好吗?当然。
Sandra, do you feel all right? Of course.
但我必须服从医生的命令。
But I must obey my doctor's orders.
哦,当然!你得按医生说的做。
Oh, sure! You gotta do what the doctor tells ya.
我打算这么做。我们去散散步吧，威尔伯。
I intend to. Let's have a walk, Wilbur.
Toodle-oo。
Toodle-oo.
教授，你了解女人吗?
Professor, do you understand women?
我甚至都没试过。我去拿杯喝的。
I don't even try. I'm gonna get me a drink.
坐在这里。
Sit here.
桑德拉，你有点奇怪。你不是你自己。
Sandra, there's something strange about ya. You're not yourself.
有什么我能帮忙的吗?是的。
Is there anything I can do to help? Yes.
我要你和我一起去岛上。
I want you to go away with me to the island.
只有我和你?是的。
Just me and you? Yes.
我想做你生命中的唯一。我想成为你的一部分。
I want to be the only one in your life. I want to be part of you.
我想融入你的血液。
I want to be in your blood.
我想我明白你的意思。
I think I know what you mean.
难道你不想要一个比我漂亮的男人吗?不。除了你，我谁也不要。
Wouldn't you want a prettier fellow than me? No. I want no one but you.
你是那么血统纯正，那么圆润，那么坚定。
You are so full-blooded, so round, so firm.
装得满满的。我想保持这种状态。
So fully packed. And I want to stay that way.
卡住了我自己。我道出了”。
Stuck myself. I'm bleedin'.
让我看看。嗯。
Let me see it. Uh-uh.
那里不够我们两个人住，如果你是这么想的话。
There ain't enough there for the two of us, if that's what you're thinking.
我告诉你我在想什么。看着我的眼睛。
I'll tell you what I'm thinking. Look into my eyes.
我害怕。没什么好害怕的。
I'm afraid to. There's nothing to be afraid of.
看。更深。
Look. Deeper.
更深层次的!
Deeper!
更深。
Deeper.
我看得够深了。我不想再看了。
I looked deep enough. I don't wanna look anymore.
你当然知道。
Of course you do.
你不知道接下来会发生什么吗?
Don't you know what's going to happen now?
我会咬人。哦,不……我要!
I'll bite. Oh, no... I will!
——威尔伯!——琼!威尔伯!
- Wilbur! - Joan! Wilbur!
琼?他在那儿。
Joan? There he is.
威尔伯，你看见琼了吗?
Wilbur, have you seen Joan?
没有，但我已经下定决心了。
No, but I have definitely made up my mind.
你可以带上桑德拉，但一定要准备好足够多的绷带。
You can have Sandra, but make sure you've got plenty of bandages.
也许德古拉把琼引诱到树林里然后…小妞，你知道如果我在树林里遇到德古拉会发生什么吗?
Maybe Dracula lured Joan into the woods and... Chick, do you know what could happen if I meet Dracula in the woods?
我会咬人。哦,不。你得排队。
I'll bite. Oh, no. You gotta stand in line.
我们不要浪费时间了。是的,让我们。
Let's not waste any time. Yeah, let's.
琼?琼?
Joan? Joan?
琼!小妞，我们找不到她。
Joan! Chick, we can't find her.
现在，让我们继续看。来吧。琼!
Now, let's keep on looking. Come on. Joan!
琼?
Joan?
小妞，我们永远找不到她的。
Chick, we're never gonna find her.
琼!
Joan!
琼?
Joan?
琼!
Joan!
小鸡吗?小鸡吗?
Chick? Chick?
他去哪儿了?小鸡!
Where did he go? Chick!
我已经厌倦找琼了。
I'm gettin' tired of lookin' for Joan.
看看他。
Look at him.
塔尔博特先生不是叫你别再戴面具了吗?
Didn't Mr. Talbot tell you not to put that mask on anymore?
你为什么要戴上它?
Now, what'd you put it on for?
现在，把面具摘下来!来吧!
Now, take the mask off! Come on!
琼?
Joan?
嘿，奇克，你在里面找什么?
Hey, Chick, now, what are you lookin' in there for?
你知道你在那里找不到琼的。
You know you're not gonna find Joan there.
现在，来吧，起来!起来!我们得找到琼。
Now, come on, get up! Get up! We gotta find Joan.
加油，奇克。现在，把面具摘掉!
Come on, Chick. Now, take that mask off!
别着急。我是你的朋友!
Take it easy. I'm your friend!
的帮助!的帮助!
Help! Help!
的帮助!
Help!
那人受伤了。好像有什么东西袭击了他。
The man's been hurt. Looks like something attacked him.
去看医生。
Get a doctor.
你会没事的，虽然再多半英寸你的颈静脉就会断了。
You'll be all right, though another half inch would have severed your jugular vein.
扶他起来。
Get him up.
是谁干的?是一个戴着狼面具的人。
Who did it? It was somebody in a wolf's mask.
麦克道格尔，你怎么了?
McDougal, what happened to you?
你!是你!他说他会抓到我的。
You! It was you! He said he was gonna get me.
我吗?这是正确的。
Me? That's right.
今晚早些时候我看到他和你吵架了。
I saw him arguing with you earlier this evening.
那太荒唐了。为什么，我不会……人，活生生的人。那是个男孩。告诉他们。
That's ridiculous. Why, I wouldn't... People, real live people. That's a boy. Tell 'em.
你,小鸡。怎么了?
You, Chick. What's the matter?
想咬我一口是什么意思?
What's the idea of trying to take a bite out of me?
这个想法是什么?现在,你。
What was the idea? Now, you.
怎么，他也咬了你一口吗?
What, did he take a bite out of you too?
你怎么了，奇克?
What's the matter with you, Chick?
你疯了还是怎么了?威尔伯!
You gone mad or something? Wilbur!
别让那个小家伙骗了你。
Don't let that little fellow fool you.
他是同谋。我吗?
He's an accomplice. Me?
我们打电话给警长吧。我去给他打电话。
Let's call the sheriff. I'll go call him.
等一下……
Wait a minute...
小鸡!小鸡!哦,小鸡!
Chick! Chick! Oh, Chick!
小鸡!德古拉伯爵要我……琼，琼，别这样。我们得离开这里。
Chick! Count Dracula wants me... Joan, Joan, come on. We gotta get outta here.
琼?
Joan?
琼?别告诉我你也疯了。
Joan? Don't tell me you've gone bats too.
威尔伯!威尔伯!威尔伯!
Wilbur! Wilbur! Wilbur!
小鸡!小鸡!
Chick! Chick!
小鸡,小鸡。安静。他们在追我。
Chick, Chick. Quiet. They're after me.
追你?为什么?
After you? What for?
麦克道格昨晚差点被狼杀死
McDougal was almost killed last night by either a wolf